Prince Harry!
Hariya!
Have you seen my cat?
Prince Harry.
Prince Harry, where are you?
PRINCE "HARIYA" HARRY
LEO "LECHEROUS" MATTHEWS
Have you seen Prince Harry?
My cat!
Prince Harry.
Fuck off!
YASH "THE JUNKIE" BATRA
Table number four and table number nine!
Is this how we're going to
serve our guests? Come on, guys!
Prince Harry!
Where is Guppie Ram?
Why isn't he here?
The old-timer has been missing
all evening.
I have no clue where he is!
Let's go! The wolves are at the gate!
Raja sahab, a new car?
Always.
At your service, my lord.
Welcome.
Buy something nice for your kids.
RANNVIJAY "THE SHOW-OFF" SINGH
I don't want to be around
either of the candidates tonight.
Their election antics
will only drain our budget.
Raja sahab, for instance.
He'll endlessly order Scotch in style.
He's a fraud.
And the waiter will put it on our tab.
And Shehnaz,
she's already offered roles in movies
to half the club
because of the elections.
See, he doesn't even answer my call.
I've called him countless times,
but he isn't answering.
And I'm sure he won't even show up today.
That Bengali woman
is turning my son into a leftist.
Mala, don't behave like a typical mom now.
"The girl is always the vamp!"
Did I say anything wrong, Mother?
So, you've been living in Kolkata
for the past three years. Fine.
But when you get back,
you should come and stay with us, right?
What's the point of coming to Delhi
if you're not going to stay with us?
Not just that,
he even sounds like that Bengali now.
- What?
- He says, "The Club is a symbol
of privilege and classism."
What class?
- Look at us.
- Exactly.
We've been rotting
in this eight-year-old car.
- What a clunker!
- No one has even offered us an umbrella.
Man, when did it start raining
in November?
Global warning.
It is warming, Mom, warming.
But it's a warning.
Prince Harry!
Prince Harry.
Hello, everyone,
gather around for the group photo.
Please come to the main stage area.
Listen, the tambola will only start
after the group photo.
Namaste, Bhaisahab.
The bar will still be open
after the photo.
Drown yourself in it if you wish.
- You can stand here and...
- Greetings!
Hey, cutie.
Did you find your cat?
Love kids.
- Please!
- Bhatti sahab!
- Come...
- Stop playing the class monitor.
Your tenure is about to end.
That's what
I have been waiting for too, Raja sahab.
Once the elections are over on Thursday,
I will dance!
Guys, the next round is on me!
Sir, you know the drinks are on the house.
AKASH "THE PITIABLE" DOGRA
Hey, Dogra!
Join us, man.
Raja sahab!
What is this, sir?
Just two tickets?
Alright, give me two more,
but don't ask me for money.
And why is your glass empty?
- Staff!
- Boy!
- There he is.
- What is this?
- Raja sahab's glass should never be empty.
- Never! "My lord!"
- Always "my lord."
- My lord.
The staff will always
call me "my lord," and...
buy something nice for your kids.
I am so proud of my Yashu. So proud!
Do you know the rehab center in the UK?
That was just fabulous!
Just fab!
Just for a few lakhs a month!
Just a few lakhs
and all your drug addiction goes
out of the window! You're squeaky clean!
ROSHNI "THE BULLSHITTER" BATRA
And you know they had
an indoor heated swimming pool,
scented towels and sushi?
I was like, "You know what?"
"I wanna fake addiction
and get admitted in here!"
- Hello.
- How are you?
- Very well.
So my "commie" son is here.
Are you sure I'm yours?
Sometimes, I feel like...
I was switched at the hospital.
Not at the hospital, son.
You've switched personalities now.
You've been in Delhi for a week
and you haven't bothered to come see me.
You haven't even called me.
I mean, who are we to you?
Tomorrow, if we were to die,
- you wouldn't even bat an eyelid. Right?
- Mom...
- I tried calling you 17 times!
- Do you even check your phone?
- Mom...
- I don't even see a blue tick...
...which means you haven't even
read the messages, son.
- Mom...
- I just asked you
to attend this Tambola Night
for your mother's sake...
I'm here, aren't I?
I'm standing right here. See?
All right, let's get the picture taken.
Come.
Mom, I don't belong
to this fancy dress competition.
Oh, okay.
You'd only "belong'"
if she were here, right?
Mom, I have nothing to do with her.
I have a steady girlfriend.
I know who's nothing,
who's steady and who's unsteady.
- I know everything...
- Okay, that's enough!
Please come for the picture.
- We have to start the tambola.
- What's with this November rain?
This is the last call!
Poor farmers.
- Hi, yeah! Excuse me.
- Sure.
Hello.
She's really worried
about the farmers, huh?
Well, she's dug her way
out of a pile of dung, so...
SHEHNAZ "THE DIVA" NOORANI
Shehnaz ji, I am so glad
you could come despite your shoot.
By the way,
magenta really suits you, I must say.
Green?
Gray?
- Gold.
- That you are.
Silver cake knife?
I don't know
where the silver cake knife is.
Go ask another waiter.
How old is that?
- My grandfather gave it to me. Original.
- Your grandfather?
Yes, my grandfather.
Excuse me.
Please stay right where you are, alright?
Everyone, please come.
Come on, take the picture.
Bhatti ji...
What's happening?
- I am still the president.
- Excuse me!
- Your tenure is almost over.
- What do you mean by that?
- Never mind.
- Okay, is everyone here?
- Yes!
- Hold on a second! Wait for us.
Hello, Mrs. Nayyar,
you're looking really pretty.
Could you please move?
- Just a bit. Come on!
- Okay.
- Hurry!
- Yes, please.
- Yeah.
- And, everybody,
- now, just give me your best smiles. Okay?
- Always the best smile!
Yeah, like a happy family.
And Shehnaz ma'am, oh, my God.
What an unforgettable smile.
Yes, madam.
Let us see your best smile today,
because after the election...
I'll be really busy
after the election, Mr. Singh.
I need to build a washroom
in the kitchen garden area, remember?
Over my dead fucking body!
If that's what it takes.
- Okay. Guys, ready?
- Yeah!
And one, two...
Oh, fuck.
BAMBI "THE WIDOW" TODI
Ma'am, are you fine?
Guys, wait.
How can you take the picture
without the prettiest girl in the club?
- Grandma...
- Let's go!
- Son, do you feel like you belong now?
- Mom...
- Guys, is anybody left? Ready?
- Smile.
And one, two...
I endured your deceit
Sipping tears, with a smile bittersweet
Breaking promises, deserting me
You walked away
Baby
Innocent, naive baby
Breaking my heart, deserting me
You walked away
Shalini.
- Sir.
- Yes?
Let me do it, please.
No, Padam.
I had pledged in front of Shalini
that I would learn how to parallel park
before I got to Lucknow.
I just have ten more days.
I had taken a pledge too.
That I'd get married last year.
I checked out 23 girls.
An average of two girls a month.
But no wedding card
has been printed yet.
That's because you're checking them out.
Try having a conversation instead.
Conversations have the power to untangle
the most intricate knots by themselves.
But the car doesn't have the power
to parallel park by itself, sir.
You need to move a little to the left.
A tiny bit.
- A tiny bit?
- A tiny bit, sir. Come on.
Yes, I'm coming.
Come, sir. Come...
You bloody... Motherfucker!
Hey, calm down. You're making it worse!
What's wrong?
Hey, are you blind?
You hit my two-million-rupee car,
you motherfucker!
Two million? Have you seen your face?
That piece of junk isn't even
worth ten rupees, you dumbfuck.
Hey, old man,
do you have buttons for eyes?
Well, it's either of the two, sir.
- Step out of the car!
- I am coming.
I'll show you.
I'll report you to the cops.
You wanna go to the police station?
- You bloody mother...
- I'll take you!
He lost his mother two days ago!
So sorry.
Sir, this is Padam Kumar ji.
Do you know what happened to him once?
What, sir?
He wanted to join the police force,
but his eyesight wasn't good enough.
He failed the examination.
Now, he teaches old-timers
and women how to drive.
And he practices belly dancing at night.
His dad attained martyrdom
in the police force.
My dad?
Be kind to him.
- Jai Hind, sir.
- It's okay.
Yes, Sub-Inspector Padam
and I are absolutely free right now.
We are fooling around in the parking area.
Which club, sir?
Sir, how long will it take?
It's Diwali, you see.
The packers and movers
are waiting for you to arrive.
And the thieves and killers
are waiting for me to leave.
Anyway, the chief said
it wouldn't take too long. It's an...
Open and shut case.
Your job is so difficult.
It's such a waste of time.
On Diwali, no less.
President sahab,
was it someone's anniversary?
It was our Diwali Tambola last night.
A raging success.
My club made three million.
But the accident was sad.
So sad.
Come in.
The Royal Delhi Club
is the country's most top-notch club.
Very exclusive.
Some Indian presidents
have played golf here too.
Right there.
The fee to become a member
is 19,9 million rupees, plus GST.
But even if you have the money,
the waiting period
is a minimum of 20 years.
Even after independence, for many years,
only the British
were allowed to be members.
I mean, not even
other white-skinned folks.
Bravo!
That really is something to be proud of.
Exactly.
You won't find a campus as large as this
anywhere else in India.
Isn't this the same club
that Highway Minister Ruhia ji
wants to shut down?
The highway minister's lazy son
came here wearing sandals.
I mean, if you want to wear sandals,
you can go to any of the numerous
roadside hotels on the highway.
We politely requested,
"Kind sir, please wear formal shoes."
Who doesn't own shoes?
I own at least 15 pairs.
- I have Prada, Gucci, everything.
- What? Pucchi?
He wouldn't budge.
We have 100-year-old rules.
- A hundred years.
- And rules are rules.
See, even he gets it.
I should have hit him
with his damn sandals!
Moron! And that was it.
A hashtag went viral
in less than thirty minutes.
#BritishBootlickerRDC.
#AntiNationalRDC.
Anti-national?
Yeah, it's quite easy to become
an anti-national these days.
Boy!
Boy, get me my cushion!
Chop, chop!
Hey, girl!
How dare you enter
the members' washroom!
Sorry, sir.
Don't mind, sir.
Normally, this doesn't happen.
Rules are rules.
This is a community bar.
Those people aren't allowed
in here either.
- Let's go.
- Come in.
The election's in three days.
And today's the day he chooses to die!
- Come inside, ACP.
- No...
Myself, SI Padam Kumar. He's the ACP...
Sir...
Sir?
Sir.
ACP Bhavani Singh.
Never mind. Come.
Leo Matthews. Zumba trainer.
So sad.
It was quick.
The barbell slipped
from the deceased's hands,
fell on his windpipe
and fractured his neck.
Time of death?
Between 5:00 and 7:00 a.m.
We'll find out
the exact time after the autopsy,
but in clear accident cases like this,
we don't need an autopsy.
Someone told me he was an orphan.
I will look for his address.
Mithun!
Alright, Doctor.
Once you and President sahab
sign this, our job here is done.
We will take the body away.
President sahab!
Can we see the CCTV footage?
What's the need?
Just a glimpse.
That's Raja sahab. Rannvijay Singh.
One of our most esteemed members.
He's from the royal family of Achingad.
And that is the gym trainer, Thinsuk.
No, I think he's Theju.
I'm not sure, they look the same.
These camera angles will definitely
have some blind spots.
- What's that?
- Nothing.
Pause.
That's the same sky-blue-colored bottle
we found near the body.
Hey, buddy!
Didn't you notice the bloody balloons
blocking your CCTV?
Normally, this doesn't happen.
What do you wanna see?
The color of the balloons?
Pause!
A cat's tail.
Prince Harry.
Prince Harry?
For the past 100 years,
we have named every pet in the club
after members of the British royal family.
You see, this club was built
to commemorate the arrival of King George.
But he couldn't come here. Busy man.
But still,
that family means everything to us.
Wow, that really is something
to be proud of.
Exactly.
So, what do we do with him, ACP?
Will you take him away or shall we?
The members need to use the gym, right?
President sahab.
What happened at your club
wasn't an accident.
- It was a murder.
- No!
We don't permit murders at my club.
And our members are all respected people.
And they all have my respect.
Balloons blocking the CCTV,
Hariya ji's health,
and a tender rumble inside my stomach,
all these things tell me
that Leo ji was murdered.
Who was the first one to see
Leo ji's body?
Sir...
I don't think we should speak
without our lawyers.
Suit yourself.
Yes, sir?
My apologies. Thank you.
This...
I am so upset.
I've been drinking all morning.
Relax, Cooks.
We will get a new Zumba trainer.
Dime a dozen.
Who cares about Zumba?
Original. Cookie Katoch Cocktail.
COOKIE "COCKTAIL" KATOCH
Beetroot juice with a little tequila.
Oh, my! Nirmal has uploaded a photo
to pay her tributes already.
Look at the damn photo she has uploaded!
Oh, my God! Look at that lip job.
Show!
Bloody bitch.
She'll never tell us who she went to.
You can ask her. She's your friend.
Ask her.
So, I was talking about Leo ji's body...
You can't imagine.
All the hairs on my arms stood up.
- Rosh! We need to go for waxing!
- Sure.
No, but listen,
Cinderella is just too crowded on Diwali.
I am not going.
Let's go to the Club's parlor.
We will give a couple
of hundred bucks to Ganga.
No way!
The body, madam. Body.
Whose?
Yeah, I was just telling you about that.
The three of us went to the gym at 7:00.
A dead body
under a three-tier strawberry cake?
And that was only the appetizer, Cooks!
After that, I'm telling you,
you're going to go crazy
listening to what happened
at Tambola Night.
Cooks aunty, why didn't you come?
You had too much to drink last night?
No, sweetie, Katoch sahab was in the mood.
So, you know, right?
He's like a...
horse in bed.
I always miss all the action at the Club
because of him.
Come on, girls. Let's go for it.
Oops!
- What are you doing?
- What...
- What am I doing?
- What are you doing?
I dropped my napkin.
You dropped your napkin?
- Rosh, don't look at me like that.
- Cooks, I know you.
- You and your wild imagination.
- Cooks...
- Guys...
- That's just gossip.
- Guys!
- What?
Cooks... Cooks, he's dead.
Are you calling the police?
Obviously.
Poor Leo.
And his amazing thighs...
What a waste.
Is it that easy to kill someone, SP?
No, it's incredibly stressful,
even for the most hardened criminals.
So the BMR must be going
through the roof, right?
They must lose about two to three kilos
just from sweating, right?
Well, then, I should definitely consider
committing a murder!
I'll lose this belly fat
and get my hips in shape.
Madam, you were talking about a dead body
under the strawberry cake.
Whose body?
- Yes, I...
- His.
Why would anyone kill him?
Guys, it's not funny.
- Poor thing.
- Cooks aunty, stop it.
Sir, he's demented.
Yuck!
Relax, guys. It's strawberry sauce.
Come on.
And where was Leo ji when this happened?
Leo was hosting the tambola.
When the lady is flirty at three and zero...
Thirty.
Fast five!
Come on.
The scoop is
that Leo was
Shehnaz Noorani's latest astronaut.
Astronaut, madam?
Well, Shehnaz is the moon.
So, there must be some
astronauts as well, right?
I was wondering if she's the same
famous actress, Shehnaz Noorani.
A C-grade heroine of B-grade films.
She divorced two husbands,
extorted a hefty alimony,
and finally settled here in Delhi.
Bloody witch!
And there's been a horde of astronauts
landing on the moon ever since.
You know what I mean?
And I'm sure you were watching
through your telescope, right, Rosh aunty?
Motu Seth is always late.
Six and eight, 68!
Full house!
And that's when the real chaos started.
- Me too!
- And Leo said...
Two Motus?
It's a scam.
There can't be two full houses.
- This old man is cheating.
- Show me your ticket.
- Move!
- Calm down, Uncle. What are you doing?
Hey, who did you call "uncle"?
Bloody item number, PE teacher.
- Gigolo! How dare you?
- What is he saying?
Vermin like him crawl out of the gutter.
Rats!
He said rats.
Rats like him crawl out of the gutter.
Cooks, man. You weren't even there.
Fine, then. Why do you need me?
You tell the tale. I am leaving.
Anyway...
After that, that Dogra boy got there...
Cockroaches like him
crawl out of the gutter.
Guys!
- I am Leo Matthews' lawyer.
- Pause.
So Leo ji's lawyer
was playing tambola as well?
Excuse me! Please move.
Akash bhaiya,
I'll lose my job because of you.
You're in court on a holiday.
Just 30 more seconds, brother.
- Hurry up.
- Listen.
- The judge will need a blood test report.
- Sir, please.
Make sure you have it.
This lab will provide it
at a reasonable cost.
- Please have a look.
- Brother, look at my documents as well.
- Look at my documents.
- Sir, help us as well.
You are our last hope, brother.
- Hello.
- Akash, Leo has been murdered.
- That MC?
- Yes.
The police want to have a word with you.
It's Diwali. I am heading back to Kolkata.
My flight is in two hours.
Does your girlfriend live with you?
Koohu.
Koohu?
Sounds like the name of a bird.
Well, what can I say?
Perhaps I am destined to end up
with girls with weird names,
Bambi.
Sir, I met Leo,
I mean, the deceased, just once.
What's happening? Why is the cop here?
He's been sitting here for
the past two hours. Get him out of here!
Three years ago. For a small case.
What was the case?
Cocaine.
Some minors
from an orphanage were involved.
The orphanage's warden
was arrested as well.
He was a cripple.
But you declared in front
of Maharaja Rannvijay Singh
that you are Leo ji's lawyer.
Sir...
people in the Club are afraid
of just two things.
Taxes and lawyers.
So I thought,
"Let's have Raja ji take the stand."
I represent Leo Matthews,
and if he wants, he can sue you
and this club for slander,
criminal intimidation
and workplace harassment.
Let it go, Raja sahab.
We can share the winnings.
That's what I was saying.
Split the bounty and have fun, Uncles.
Raja sahab never shares his belongings.
- What are you laughing about?
- Why are you lying, my lord?
- You bloody...
- Get lost!
I didn't mean...
I didn't mean that!
Baby
Innocent, naive baby
Breaking my heart, deserting me
You walked away
I endured your deceit
Sipping tears, with a smile bittersweet
Breaking promises, deserting me
You walked away
Baby
I saw Bambi dancing
in the midst of the chaos.
Only Bambi could do that.
No, not like this.
Hold it like this. Like this.
- Upwards?
- Yeah, upwards.
Baby
Innocent, naive baby
Breaking my heart, deserting me
You walked away
They have given us this junkyard
to finish our interrogation.
Sir, this Bhatti fucker...
Well, if you're doing cleaning,
Happy Diwali!
Happy Diwali, sir.
According to President sahab,
it was one of you
who made the protein shake.
But he isn't sure who.
Sir, do you think we both look the same?
Yes, I made the protein shake. So?
Sir, he's also the one who
places weights on the barbell.
All you do is complain.
Sir, this guy Leo,
doesn't do anything on his own.
He thinks he is over and above us.
Was.
There you go. He never liked Leo, sir.
He made more money
than the two of us combined.
Plus, all the ladies always asked for him.
Hey, I am not interested
in those "Aunty.coms."
Sir, my girlfriend is 50 times
more beautiful than them.
Wait, I will show you her photo.
Wait, sir.
Minu, sir.
Did you know Leo ji?
Just the usual pleasantries.
MINU "THE CHEAT" DIMRI
Thank you.
Actually, that aqua aerobic thing
was my idea, sir.
Leo stole that from me.
- Aqua...
- Aqua aerobics, Padam.
It's a water sport.
It was your idea? Leo stole it?
Bambi!
You're still here?
There's a small village near Kolkata.
It was hit by a storm.
A primary school lost its roof.
So Koohu's going there
with her volunteer friends.
And you're still here.
Dreamgirl.
That's what they call the girls
working in the Club's beauty parlor.
Hair tong burns.
Members with curly hair want it straight,
and those with straight hair want curls.
And how did you know Leo?
I handle everything, from the kitchen,
to waiting tables, to gardening,
and even babysitting
the Club members' children.
I know who killed Leo.
The cold cuts through to the bone.
In our Garhwal, a man
was carrying an ax on his shoulder.
He was shivering because of the cold.
Suddenly, he sneezed,
and the ax fell on his neck...
and...
He used to talk so much nonsense
that he earned the nickname "Guppie Ram."
But post dementia,
these days, it's hard to tell...
Whether Guppie is chattering away
or if his own mind
is echoing that chatter to him.
Don't you miss...
this place?
This is the exact spot
where I first laid eyes on
the Bambi Todi, exactly 19 years ago.
Back when I was
four inches taller than you.
Back when you faked drowning...
- Please!
- ...hoping I'd come to your rescue.
Even if I were really drowning,
I would rather die
than have a crush on you!
That's for you. Congratulations!
The more I try to forget you
The more you come to mind
I remember you just as much
What do you want from me?
Why did you call me here?
- I need to talk to you.
- What do you wanna talk about?
What is it? Tell me.
- I need to tell you something important...
- Bambi!
- Can you come here, please?
- Where is he at?
Give me a second. Please wait for me.
As much as I try to console my heart
Happy anniversary, Bambi and Anshul!
I remember you just as much
As much as I try to console my heart
My life slips away
"Darling, are you okay?"
My mom just needs an excuse to text me.
A widow, you see?
I was planning to come and see you,
but my mom told me that you
and Anshul's mom had gone to Manali
to look for his body.
You could have come later.
Anyway, one phone call in three years?
You could have
at least called me once, Dogra.
I still remember that phone call.
The police said
that they only found 21 bodies.
They said four...
four bodies must have washed away
in the river.
I couldn't believe my luck.
The rumors were true!
Akash Dogra has given up his pseudo-war
against the class system
because he wanted to take a dip
at The Royal Delhi Club.
Have you heard about Junior Batra?
The one who went to rehab?
Apparently, he taught the staff there
how to snort drugs,
straight out of their asses!
- Hey, asshole!
- Bastard!
- You dick!
- Sit on it!
Asshole, I have been clean
for the past ten months.
I haven't even smoked a cigarette.
What the hell!
Fuck you, Bambi!
Sorry, Batra.
Man, I had my phone with me.
Oh, shit.
Motherfucking morons!
Call me when you get home.
It's one of the two trainers, obviously.
There's a ton of infighting.
Theju, Theja, whatever.
They look the same.
No. Theju ji is from Karnataka,
and Thinsuk ji is from Arunachal Pradesh.
Exactly!
Whatever.
Do the members of this old British club
think they're British as well?
Lord knows what other illegal activities
these great "liberals"
might be up to behind closed doors
of the Club.
If the investigation into this case
isn't carried out diligently,
we'll have to take matters
into our own hands.
Shut up! Lowlife!
If the case isn't resolved swiftly,
they will shut down our club.
Ten days.
Would that be swift enough?
I'll adjust.
Let's go!
My tenants might move out of my house,
but no one forgets the tea I make!
No one forgets me either.
It's the grinding stone.
That's the real secret
to a slurp-worthy tea.
There you go.
You're from Haryana, right?
I can tell just by looking
at your mustache.
Jaat boys!
Haryanvi songs have a vibe.
Hindi songs just don't cut it anymore.
This is the first time
the cops are in my house.
This surely calls for a selfie, sir.
Come on.
Smile.
I'll bring in the whole squad,
if you wish.
- Sir!
You think you're in your aunt's house?
Looks like we're gonna need
some strong and special tea.
- Let's go to the room then.
- What?
- Leo ji's.
- Yeah, sure.
- It's been a crazy day, sir.
- I will deal with you two later.
Preparing food for your constables
and making tea for them.
We treat our guests like family.
Oh, my!
It seemed alright this morning.
This must be your constables, sir.
No one's been upstairs all morning.
I'll deal with you two
at the police station!
- Get lost!
- Sir!
Sir, whose pictures are these?
These aren't just pictures, Padam.
This is the loose end of this case.
Ma'am, do you think something's missing
from this mess?
He had one of those...
The big one...
It's something between
a phone and a computer.
Trimmer.
- Tablet.
- Yes, that.
He had a red tablet.
He used to be glued to it all day,
watching his own movies.
So, he was also a filmmaker?
- Padam.
- Yes, sir.
Leo ji seems to be a lively,
fun-loving individual.
Wait a minute.
It's mine.
I used to come upstairs quite often.
I must have dropped it.
Uncle, can you fasten the hook?
Please?
Sir, why don't you wear the uniform?
Padam, the uniform is a barrier
between us and the people.
When I lose that barrier,
I become one of them.
And that's when they're more likely
to spill the finer details.
It's way more effective than a baton.
Come on, sir!
The baton's like a magic wand!
To each their own.
Kashi, I need to tell you something.
- Leo was blackmailing me.
- What?
- Bambi, you stole the ACP's glasses?
- Yes.
Still?
I had quit.
But after Anshul's accident...
- I don't know. It started again.
- Started again?
I pick up random stuff.
And I don't even realize it!
Glasses, gold bangles,
toilet paper, dentures!
Why?
Dentures?
Just once.
Bambi, man!
I've spent half my life
putting back the stuff you've stolen.
But you weren't here this time.
So, tell me.
Should we inform the Hindi professor?
Not just inform, we must return it.
Bambi.
I don't trust you. Give it to me.
Come on!
Bambi.
Stop it!
So, Leo got to know about this?
And you know my mom.
She's always been a mess.
And you know
how the people at the Club are.
Of course.
If they found out...
Anyway...
- Now what?
- I will show you.
Listen to this.
Whenever Leo sent me the song,
it meant, "Show me the money."
Forgive me, but...
Shalini has taken all the furniture away
with her to Lucknow.
- Shalini?
- Shalini...
- Better half.
- Much better half, Padam.
Sir, why are you moving out of Delhi?
Because of the cold or the pollution?
Delhi's crime, Todi.
Mrs. Shalini might have had enough
of the murderers,
blackmailers and kleptomaniacs.
Sorry, sir.
If I don't have the nearsighted one...
Sir, you remember the kids
I had gotten out on bail?
Leo used to force her to donate money
to their orphanage.
Leo ji's phone
has no evidence of blackmail.
Sir, but my chat?
Leo ji has deleted all his chats.
But it's still there on my phone.
The rumble in my stomach...
tells me...
that you were not the only one
Leo ji was blackmailing.
Sir, this case keeps getting more complex.
How will we close it in ten days?
Ten days?
Yes, in ten days,
if I don't report to Shalini in Lucknow
and the government as well,
or if my transfer order gets deferred,
then she will find a poet
and get married to him.
Sir.
By the way,
a poet and a detective are two sides
of the same coin.
Absolutely.
One unravels riddles,
and the other solves them.
Just like the
world's most complicated riddle...
- Lo...
- Love.
So, have you ever been on this train?
After so many years, finally,
I am going to gift you a new car.
How about that?
I just had a déjà vu moment
from my childhood.
What did I do now?
You remember you used
to get me imported gifts
just to maintain the standard
of your social circle?
Fine.
I will gift you a car
that matches your standards. Okay?
Nice, cute, comfy, middle-class car.
Is that fine?
I am good with this middle-class car.
He was Leo Matthews to everyone else.
But to us, he was Lambodhar.
Sir, when he was a child,
he misbehaved all the time,
on purpose,
just so that nobody would adopt him.
Because I would be left alone...
and there wasn't much demand
for someone like me.
- What about those donations, Warden ji?
- It was all because of Leo, sir.
He developed numerous contacts
through his new job.
Big people with big hearts.
He said, "Raks,
these fancy rich people spend more money
on a bottle of wine
than my monthly salary."
And the donations just started pouring in.
Warden, my brother,
those weren't donations.
Your God-like brother, Lambodhar,
was blackmailing people.
This basketball court...
- Perhaps I donated it.
- So?
You guys are unbelievable.
Leo racked up these funds
by taking some major risks.
You think that was easy?
He was a goddamn Robin Hood.
Yeah, right!
Madam, did you locate
any of the members' names in there?
Fuck me!
What is it?
Who else is on the list?
What? There was no blackmail!
The boy was a magician!
From UK-6 to UK-4 in three months.
- Just like that!
- U...
Size... My size.
Cookie didn't manage to lose any.
She gained three kilograms.
Anyway, when Leo informed me about his...
NGO, orphanage,
I offered to donate myself. I mean...
Leo.
Don't do this.
- I will do anything.
- Really?
I will.
Sign the fucking check, bitch!
Smart.
Madam, you recognize any of these?
You found this at Leo's?
That bitch!
Kanchan!
Jasmeet.
Guppie Ram ji!
Guppie ji, over here.
If you're so eager to listen in
on our conversation,
come on in, don't be shy.
- I am unable to find my Harry.
- You might find him inside.
Hey, Hariya!
My child.
My child!
Guppie Ram ji,
your cat must be over there.
My child!
Our Guppie Ram has grown so old.
When Yashu was a kid,
he'd always be chasing after him.
- My child!
- Guppie, when Yash leaves for America...
Harry!
...I will give his polo T-shirts
and summer clothes to you.
You'll look handsome.
The wool melts,
but synthetic doesn't. It's strong.
So, what you must do is...
Guppie, are you okay?
What happened?
I can't find my Harry.
He must be outside, Guppie. Outside.
Poor people should die young.
Old age is so hard for them.
Well, I... I'm 48.
Am I allowed to live until I retire?
Everyone is being so serious.
What? Nobody has got a sense of humor?
Rich people can't even crack a joke?
Is that what you're...
Yes, Krishnan, what's the news?
What? Pinko what?
ACP, I'll leave now.
- I will call you back.
- Okay, I will see you.
Madam!
Sit down. Come here. Sit.
Do you know what happened to Padam once?
Padam was on the night shift.
Poor guy was catching some sleep.
The moment he opened his eyes, his pants...
Were missing?
No, they were just soaking wet.
Then everyone at the station
started pulling his leg.
After many days,
Padam discovered that a sniffer dog
had developed an affinity
for his trousers,
marked its territory
and then swiftly made its exit.
Think about it.
One's fault, another's blame.
Did that B-grade heroine
say something about me?
Or was it Raja ji?
That show-off Maharaja
is definitely hiding something
behind his shiny sherwani.
I am telling you that!
But why would Leo ji blackmail Raja ji?
Well, rumor has it
that your Maharaja ji
gets a special visit every night
from his "Dreamgirl."
Ganga...
Rosh aunty, that's not fair.
Sir, she's been through a lot.
She used to work at my house,
but her scumbag, piece-of-shit husband
used to beat her up regularly.
Then he abandoned her.
So, I got her a job
at the salon at the Club.
I don't know why all the Club members
gossip about her a lot.
Perhaps because she's pretty.
I've got a nose for these things, darling.
And just imagine,
if this information gets out,
Raja ji's reputation
will be in the gutter.
Enough of a motive, basically.
Raja ji, we were just...
We were talking...
"At your service!"
You already ruined my golf game.
Now, don't fuck up my card party!
He was on the list?
- Have a seat, Raja ji.
- "My lord!"
"My lord, have a seat!"
- Hello, sir. Hi, sir.
- Hello.
Raja sahab, your flare gun?
Yes!
- Keep it in the club cabinet.
- Yes, sir.
That's for you. Keep it.
Keep it like you always do.
Keep it. Don't feel shy.
- Come on, man, keep it!
- Yes, sir.
I love my staff.
I always take care of them.
How old is your gun, my lord?
A hundred years old, Inspector sahab.
A hundred years.
My grandfather,
Raja sahab Rajyavardhan Singh,
blasted the jewels off a bunch of Brits
with this bad boy.
Jewels?
Balls, dear Bambi, balls!
The Club's got just two,
and they both belong to me!
No-balls land.
- Thank you.
By the way,
those were the golden days, my lord.
- The times of kings and kingdoms.
- Yes.
These days,
we are just stuck in this election mess.
You know, this Noorani,
honestly, I don't even know
why she is fighting this election.
She keeps on shouting,
"Change, change, change!"
Why the fuck change something
which is perfect?
Sorry for the language.
Shehnaz aunty wants to build washrooms
for the female staff.
There are none.
And where does she want to build them?
In place of the kitchen garden?
Rani Vasudha Devi Garden.
My beloved wife.
Smelly staff toilets on that garden?
How fucking disgusting!
Vasudha aunty's garden will be just fine.
You're going to win the election anyway.
- So, you decide. Okay?
- Love you.
And, sir, if you need anything,
give me a call.
- I will sign for it. Bye.
- No, this is enough.
- Shall I leave?
- No...
We haven't even started yet.
Yeah, come on. You're wasting my time.
To blackmail you,
has Leo ji ever sent you a song
or a link to donate to an orphanage?
Who the fuck do you think
will blackmail me? Who?
Motherfucker!
My family has scaled
a mountain of corpses to get here!
Bloody gigolo!
I dare you to open your mouth
in front of anyone!
It's empty, you dumbfuck!
Ronnie.
Aren't you getting late for the Club?
You still gotta pick up a rental
from the mechanic.
What will you pick? Mercedes or BMW?
Go fuck yourself!
Fuck yourself!
I'll fucking fuck you!
Gym.
Yes, after the gym,
were you with someone?
If you want to ask me about Ganga,
then you'd better do it openly.
It's the women here
who beat around the bush.
Or have they stopped hiring men
in the police force?
You don't have my permission to leave.
Sit down, Raja sahab.
"Sit down, my lord."
- When did your wife die?
- Four years ago.
Padam, check the report
from the orphanage to see if
after the demise of Mrs. Babula Devi...
Vasudha Devi!
Yes, see if he began donating right after
Vasudha Devi passed away,
or if it's only been
for the past couple of months...
Yes, sir.
- Inspector...
- ACP.
Assistant Commissioner of Police
Bhavani Singh.
Now, you may leave, my lord.
Men like me,
we'll look the enemy in the eye
when we kill them.
Not like...
Not like?
Cut! The blood is too fucking pink, man!
I can't feel my neck.
Hey, get me the lemonade!
Wow.
Madam, why did you think
of becoming the club president?
Would you ask a man
the same question, ACP sahab?
Perhaps you aren't aware
that it's no longer a man's world.
Madam, where were you
after Tambola Night?
Raja sahab suggests
that you might have killed Leo.
He might have threatened to expose
details of your flings...
Affairs.
Details of your affairs to everyone.
Is that right?
If I had murdered him,
you wouldn't have found his body.
I would have chopped him
into little pieces and fed him to crows.
Crows love human meat. Did you know that?
That was dialogue from this movie.
It's a delicious character.
Whenever her heart is broken,
she commits a murder.
Leo ji was blackmailing a lot of people.
He used to ask them to donate
to the Shepherd's Home Orphanage.
Your name was on the donors' list as well.
Where are the files, Leo?
Very nice.
This must be your life's best performance.
- Hey! Should I film this?
- Screw you!
First, admit it in front of everyone.
I just can't. I have two daughters.
Really?
You can check my bank records, ACP sahab.
I have been donating
to Shepherd's for the past 20 years.
Nothing to do with blackmail.
What do you think?
Who must have killed Leo?
You get paid to find that out, ACP sahab.
Ma'am, your shot is ready.
Excuse me.
Sir, shall we leave?
Soon. Water.
Pinko Hathini is its street name.
Very powerful.
It has no odor, and it's impossible
to detect through taste.
His stomach had a minimum
of 280mg of Pinko.
Is it possible
that our muscular friend might
have taken it to pump his physique
and, in the process,
pumped out of existence?
Pinko works the other way around.
It's an opiate.
The moment you put it in your mouth,
it dissolves and enters your bloodstream,
and then your system slows down.
Your muscles start feeling like jelly
and your bones like rubber.
That means a person
might not even be able to lift this cup,
let alone a barbell.
Krishnan, tell me something.
How soon would Leo ji start feeling
the effects after taking this drug?
It affects you at bullet speed.
Just like a sexy pink elephant
kicking your central nervous system.
So, the drugs found
in the sky-blue bottle, that...
It was a normal protein shake, Singh.
But we found traces
of Pinko in another place.
The cat's vomit.
So, Prince Harry is a drug addict?
You should have seen Rosh aunty.
You just should have seen her
fucking face.
She didn't even see it coming,
and Professor sahab took her to task.
It was really something else.
You really don't have
anything better to do, right?
Better than a murder investigation? No.
Better than a murder investigation.
Dude.
What the fuck!
Didi, give me something to eat.
Give me something to eat.
What? I am really stuffed.
Giving the leftovers from your plate
doesn't make you noble, Todi.
Listen, Kashi...
Put this back, or Professor sahab
might put you behind bars.
I was talking about him
when you interrupted me.
So, Rosh aunty was like,
"Raja sahab" and suddenly, he comes in
from the back, and her face falls.
That was hysterical.
And just then, ACP got a call
about Pinki or Pinko something.
And then Raja sahab comes in
- with his flare gun...
- Wait, did he say Pinko?
- Can you let me finish?
- Did he say Pinko?
- Yes!
- Pinko Hathini?
Yes. And then Raja sahab says,
"Dear Bambi, balls..."
Leo ji started his exercise.
The day was Sunday.
What kind of workout did he do on Sundays?
Upper body, sir.
And what's the exercise
he starts his workout with?
Bench press, sir.
So, if it weren't a Sunday
and he wasn't working on his upper body,
the plan wouldn't have worked.
So what does that tell us?
- Maybe we should start with squats, sir.
- No.
The murderer was well aware
of Leo ji's routine.
Sir, I didn't do anything.
Sir, I am not interested in extra money
and all those Botox Barbies.
- Sir, I have a very beautiful girlfriend...
- Yes, I know. Enough.
He's definitely our guy.
I'm 200% sure!
He's the one who made the shake.
The bottle didn't have
any traces of Pinko, Padam.
That means, between Leo's death
and us getting here,
someone switched the bottles.
And the entire Club was already here
when we arrived.
That poor ACP.
He has no idea about this world.
I know you are doing this
to spend time with me.
Hello, please! If there is anywhere
we can find out where Pinko came from,
then this is the place.
I have stuff more potent than Pinko.
Pinko is overhyped for no good reason.
The rich people and their antics!
Hey, give me that.
Look.
Here you go.
Only a few tablets left.
If the Club members want it,
who do they go to?
They come to me.
But don't expect me to start spillin'
the names of the members.
Tell me.
My guy used to work there
three years ago. AK.
But he suddenly disappeared.
Into thin air!
He was the biggest dealer
around the club. AK bastard!
Did you know him?
Yes, Ajay Kumar. Motherfucker!
Ajay...
- Ganga's husband, Ajay Kumar?
- What?
- Were they married?
- Yes!
He used to beat her.
Akash, he used to beat her
every fucking day.
And didn't he say
he disappeared three years ago?
I don't know how many kids' lives
he must have ruined.
He was even jailed.
But that fucker got out on bail.
Now what?
Todi, no!
These people are very dangerous.
Todi, I fight cases against these drugs.
I am that lawyer.
It's for research.
It's for research?
Fuck! I don't like this!
Okay. Bambi, I need to tell you something.
Fuck!
Oh, fuck! Yash!
I thought that the rehab worked.
Maybe Rosh aunty doesn't know about this,
or Leo...
Akash, let's see what we find
at Yash's home.
Bambi, man...
I can barely walk.
And now we're breaking and entering.
Oh, God. Bambi.
Bro...
I was on a walk...
Dog. Potty.
Moon reflection.
Good windows. Good car.
- Can I come inside?
- Potty outside, bro.
Yash!
Epic party, bro.
It was so much fun.
Epic party.
You enjoy.
Who stopped the music, motherfucker?
"Epic party, bro!"
Should we tell Professor sahab about Yash?
We've known Batra since we were kids.
It will ruin his life.
Who knows, maybe his drugs
have no connection to this murder.
Akash Dogra.
How does that huge heart
even fit in your body?
Perhaps that's why you break it
into tiny little pieces,
so that it can fit inside my body.
Bye, Dogra.
Hey, Harry, where have you gone, my son?
Your dad has brought milk for you.
My child, where are you?
I have been carrying this milk for you,
and you keep wandering around.
What is my cake doing outside?
What's burning?
Har...
Oh, no!
My child!
Bambi, can you keep that phone away?
Akash, remember this
from Yash's room last night?
I have seen it.
No, you haven't. See this.
Shit! Ajay Kumar?
- Ganga's husband.
- Yash's dealer.
He must have supplied Pinko to Yash.
Looks like I'm still on
your list of suspects.
Padam won't let me
take your name off the list.
- And Mr. Singh?
- He's helpless.
I was talking about Mr. Rannvijay Singh.
Raja ji.
Padam believes Raja ji would have
looked his enemy in the eye
before killing him.
Like a real man.
- Man?
- Man.
The world's carried the weight of
male masculinity for too long, ACP sahab.
And anyway,
their masculinity is either displayed
in front of wives and children at home,
or as a part of the crowd,
in front of the weak and vulnerable.
Tell Mr. Singh to try and give birth
after enduring 14 hours of pain
in the middle of a burning chawl,
with sword-wielding rioters
at his doorstep!
And then...
Put your phone on silent!
Where is that Warden Rakesh?
Leo used to speak very highly of him.
We haven't been able to trace Rakesh ji
since yesterday.
He's missing.
Thank you so much for coming, bro.
I won't be there every time, Raks.
Why'd you have to make a scene
at the police station after getting drunk?
What wrong did I do?
I went there just to tell them that I know
who killed Leo.
What? Are you okay?
Do you want some water?
- Do you have a smoke, bro?
- Smoke...
I don't smoke.
Leo ji had a dark red tablet.
Did you see it?
Those rich bastards did it together.
They all killed him, Bhavani ji!
Oh, no!
Bloody fucking murderers!
You really seem to love this car.
- Rakesh ji!
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Hi, how are you?
- All the best for the election.
- Yes, thank you. Vote for me.
- Hi! How are you?
- All good!
Please.
Sir, should I bring a flowerpot as well?
Why go to Lucknow?
You can settle here!
Queen Victoria is here.
She will keep you company.
Do you know, Padam,
which staff member
didn't come to the church yesterday?
Who?
Guppie Ram ji.
You didn't come
to bid farewell to your friend?
He was a sinner!
He used to steal people's secrets.
Never kept anything to himself.
Bloody gossipmonger.
Guppie Ram ji, isn't that too much water
for the beetroot plant?
He went overboard.
His sins caught up to him.
Just like the other guy.
Other guy?
Who are you referring to, Guppie ji?
Guppie ji?
Oh, great! Another party's here!
How can I help you?
Tell me, how can I help?
The other...
Brother, Raja sahab is the murderer!
You insolent swine!
Call him "my lord."
It's Bhatti!
I bet you 50 bucks, motherfucker!
I bet 100 bucks
on Shehnaz Noorani.
Looks like you have met my daughters,
Shahana and Era.
Shahana ji and Era ji, I am Bhavani ji.
For you.
- I am not even a voter here.
- It's fine.
Your better half...
I am a single mother,
and that's more than enough.
ACP sahab, you're quite unlike
the detective in my movie.
How so?
Detective Bose is always undercover.
And those cliché dialogues.
"The dreaded savage killer!"
But what I love about you
is that you're real.
The truth is that most killers
are not savages.
We know and recognize them.
Sometimes even fall in love with them.
Ordinary men and women.
Like me.
Like you.
Very well. Another place
where we are competing with men.
See you later.
- Sir.
- Yes, these artifacts are really popular.
Sir, all this is Cookie aunty's talent.
And Cooks aunty is so generous
that she keeps gifting
- these "artifacts" to people.
- Baby.
And people quietly throw it away
in the Club's storeroom.
By the way, whose statues are these?
The two candidates.
Really?
Which one is Shehnaz ji?
Obviously, this one is Shehnaz ji!
I had seen her movie. Isn't she beautiful?
Pack whatever food is left
and keep it in my car.
Take this.
You know the shiny blue Mercedes?
That one. Okay?
For the poor.
- I hate wastage.
- Please pack it.
Have you lost it?
You think I'm gonna let you ruin
my stomach just because your cat died?
How dare you put my sausage
in that bloody microwave, you fool!
Get lost, Guppie!
I'll water the plants.
I already watered it. What should I do?
Are you okay?
Sit here.
Did Yash say something to you?
Are you missing Harry?
I killed Harry.
I have lost my mind.
How could I do it?
I burned him in the oven.
You left the oven door open by mistake.
It wasn't your fault.
If she wins, it's over!
It's all over!
- I...
- It will be alright, Guppie.
Everything will be alright.
Akash, I am very worried about Guppie.
But seriously...
Born to one, now taken away by another
Oh Lord, my Almighty!
Cheers!
Listen, I will leave first.
You come out after two minutes. Okay?
Yash!
Does it look like a murder
happened here three days ago?
- Yash!
- And that the murderer is one of them.
Who must be discreetly patting
themselves on the back saying...
"Murder Mubarak!"
I know everything about you!
Asshole, you got here before I did,
motherfucker!
Hey! What happened?
- What's going on?
- Hey!
How dare you touch me, motherfucker?
- Hey, stop it!
- I will sue them!
- Don't talk to them!
- Be quiet!
Asshole, you became a lawyer
just by studying through correspondence!
- Hey, shut up!
- Mala!
I will sue you! I will sue your family.
Move back!
- Move back!
- Get back!
- Move! Let me through!
- Enough.
- One second.
- I am the president.
Move back. Raja ji, move back.
Come on.
Yes. Madam, stop right there.
Come, dear.
- Bambi, let's go.
- Take care of her.
- Let's go.
- Thanks, Raja sahab.
Come with me. Come.
Let's go.
The murderer blew Guppie Ram's brains out
and put the gun in his hand
to make it look like a suicide.
It appears that Guppie Ram ji
was quite the coffee enthusiast.
He has sacks full of coffee!
Don't. Stop it.
I said stop!
Yashu, I spoke to your dad.
There's nothing to worry about.
- I will talk to them. What's...
- Just shut the fuck up.
It's way above your pay grade.
Dad will handle this.
Look pleasant
and keep your mouth shut.
You can do this for me, right, Rosh... Mom?
When you heard the gunshot,
where were you...
- Dear Yash.
- ...dear Yash?
He's a complete psycho, sir.
Do you know he's still taking drugs?
Your favorite Pinko Hathini.
Leo was using this
to blackmail Rosh aunty.
That Uttarakhand rehab
was a torture cell.
They used to tie him
to the floor in extreme cold.
Watery lentil soup and dense rotis.
He stayed in that hell for six months
with those dirty,
smelly hillbilly addicts.
He somehow managed to
land an internship in Boston.
But Leo found out.
And he threatened to tell his employers.
Guppie ji told me
that Leo ji's sins caught up to him.
Just like the other guy.
Who could that be?
Ganga's husband, sir.
Ajay Kumar. He's been missing
for the past three years.
And he was the one
who was selling drugs to Yash.
I told him that I was not interested
in living off his dirty money.
Cleaning, sweeping, dusting.
I did everything.
He used to think
that me and my employers...
You didn't file a police report?
Does the police pay heed
to people like us, sir?
I just informed Raja sahab.
Yes, it's mine.
It was stolen
from the Club's cabinet last night.
What is your relationship with Raja sahab?
Is there only one type of relationship
between the rich and the poor?
Nothing more?
He hasn't laid a hand on me till this day.
One second. Are you trying to imply
that I am responsible
for Ajay Kumar's disappearance?
And that I killed Guppie?
It fits perfectly, don't you think?
Next time, don't you dare drag me in here
without a shred of evidence, Inspector.
Raja ji,
those balls belong to the government.
I know you have Pinko at your home.
My team is conducting a forage operation
as we speak.
Search.
My son can't murder anyone!
And you, madam?
Rosh aunty was involved as well.
I bet at night,
the son might have added the Pinko,
and in the morning,
the mother switched the bottles.
We sent a team to search Yash ji's room.
- And?
- They didn't find anything there.
Absolutely nothing.
Let's assume that photo is from that room.
But besides that, we...
Having an epiphany?
What happened?
The earrings that I gave you
for your 20th birthday.
I saw them in Leo's evidence box.
That's what happened.
Akash, it was just physical.
After Anshul's accident, I was lost.
I was disoriented.
I used to stay awake and cry all night.
I just needed someone and...
I have heard there are plenty of flights
between Delhi and Kolkata.
How many times did I call you?
Did you bother answering?
My husband died, Kashi.
So, I am really sorry
if this was about me.
And he was there for me.
You weren't.
You know what?
Fuck you, Todi!
I wasn't there?
I was always there for you!
Like a fucking fool,
always standing next to you.
I always stood by you like a loser!
I don't know what you want from me.
One thing is clear.
I was just a timepass for you
three years ago
and I'm still a timepass today.
I'm done with you!
Man, I...
You ruined my bloody life!
And you didn't even realize it!
Why?
What did I ever do to you?
How did your husband die?
- Sir, I...
- Bambi madam!
It's time to tell the truth!
What was the real reason
for the blackmail?
Was it your klepto-mess
or your current affair?
Speak.
I didn't give a shit
if he told anybody about the affair.
If you really didn't give a shit,
why hide this shit all this time?
I didn't want Kashi to know.
You'll stay away from this case now.
- Leave. Right now.
- Sir, I...
Go on.
Now Bambi Todi's a murder suspect too.
The people of this club
might seem high-class,
roaming around with an air of arrogance,
but in reality,
they are worse than roadside thugs.
I hope the minister shuts this club down.
He has my support.
Don't punish your stomach
for your heartache, Lawyer sahab.
An octopus has three hearts.
Sir, you must be thinking why
I'm feeding you beetroot of all things.
Oh, no.
These beetroots are delicious.
Guppie Ram ji's beetroots
were a real downer!
They looked really absurd.
He used to water those plants
all day and night.
That's where he went wrong.
The thing is,
beetroot is a root vegetable.
One shouldn't overwater
beets and root vegetables.
But that's exactly what he used to do.
It makes them very wrinkly and moldy.
Isn't that too much water
for the beetroot plant?
It appears that Guppie Ram ji
was quite the coffee enthusiast.
Who's the other sinner?
Forgive me. I have an emergency.
- Sir, your dinner?
- No, perhaps some other time.
Who the hell allowed this?
The results
haven't been declared yet, Bhatti!
Motherfucker, I will bury you right here!
The times of the kings
and their kingdoms are over, my lord.
Don't fuck with me today, Shehnaz!
Did you find gold? Gold...
- Madam, don't get too excited.
- Get back.
Move the dirt carefully.
Ask everyone to step back. Back.
Padam.
Guppie Ram ji wasn't
watering the vegetables.
He was pouring acid into the ground.
There was coffee
and vinegar in the canister.
So that whoever this is
would dissolve quickly.
That's why the beetroot...
Move back.
- I have been eating...
- Stay back.
- ...these beetroots for ages.
- Madam, come back.
This is not beetroot. Bloody cannibals...
Are you here to arrest her?
- Can it wait an hour?
- No, it's urgent.
Yes.
I can't tell if it's my husband
just by looking at the bones.
Madam, when was the last time
you saw your sweetheart?
I mean your husband.
When did you last see him?
At her anniversary party.
Three years ago?
Did Raja sahab barbecue him
the same night?
Are you in touch with your in-laws?
It's a male, 25 to 30 years old.
Has been buried for over three years.
The death was due to blunt force trauma
with a heavy object.
Directly on the face.
We're trying to look
for Ajay Kumar's dental records
to do a DNA match.
There's something important
I wanted to show you.
We found these small shards
in his left eye socket.
This could be from your murder weapon.
Why was Leo blackmailing you?
Can't you see?
Can you see any bone china cups...
any Mercedes...
or any elephants?
Rannvijay Singh is just the tenant
on the ground floor of an old mansion.
That's it.
I patiently wait for the clock
to strike four, ACP.
So I can head to The Royal Delhi Club
and transform into Raja sahab.
But if that scoundrel Leo
had spilled the beans,
not just the members,
even the staff would have ridiculed me.
They would've laughed
at my twenty-rupee tip...
and thrown fifty rupees back at me.
You are telling the truth, Raja sahab,
but not the whole truth.
We discovered many such photos
at Leo's house.
If someone finds out
that a man from the royal family...
I really loved my wife.
She was the only one who understood me.
Understood who I am.
Please don't share this with anyone.
So that night, you were with Thinsuk?
I'd advise you
to come out and accept this relationship
without any hesitation. This case...
I won't be able to live with it.
I can't do this to Thinsuk.
His life will be ruined.
I request you to please give me
the remaining photos.
I will always be grateful to you.
I promise you.
If we come across
any more photographs,
I will hand them to you.
What do you mean?
Forgive me,
but I have to place you under arrest.
Let's go.
Just give me a minute.
Tanzanite.
It's expensive. Pricey, you know.
That's why I only made two of these.
- And you sold both of them.
- No.
I always gift the special ones.
Poor Raja sahab.
After his wife's death...
he was very lonely.
That was when I gifted it to him.
- And the second one?
- No, not the second. His first wife.
The second Mother Teresa.
- Sir, please tell us something.
- Sir!
No criminal can outrun
the long arm of the Delhi Police.
Not even the king
of a dilapidated mansion.
The lecherous king of the dilapidated
mansion was the murderer.
Was Raja sahab having an affair
with a girl as young as his daughter?
- I gifted the other one as well.
- Who did you give it to?
Did Raja ji bury Ganga's husband,
Ajay Kumar, in the Club?
In a garden named after his wife
Vasudha Devi...
I will kill that bastard!
- Who received the second gift?
- Sorry. My blood pressure is increasing.
- Don't shout, SP! Please leave.
The Delhi Police have solid evidence.
Ganga's husband, Ajay Kumar,
has been missing for three years
after his fight with Raja sahab.
Sir, why are you not sharing
all the details with us?
Sir, you have to tell us the truth!
Rannvijay Singh kept opposing
digging up that garden.
Cookie, who received
the second Mother Teresa?
His ancestral mansion...
Dogras.
Maharaja Rannvijay Singh...
Thank you, Cookie ji. Thank...
No, SP.
I...
What are you doing?
Katoch sahab is inside.
He will not like this.
Padam, are you ready?
Yes, this is the biggest breaking news!
- Ajay Kumar is alive!
- Sir, Ajay Kumar is still alive!
Here is Ajay Kumar in the flesh!
So the question remains,
who does the skeleton found
in RDC belong to?
What was I supposed to do?
My wife was hooking up with her bosses.
That lawyer, Dogra, was after me!
Bloody swine!
So, I went into hiding.
I could have gotten off the hook
with the police in a few weeks,
but I don't know what his deal was.
He could make all my stuff disappear.
Pinko.
Thank you for meeting me.
Are you leaving?
I remember you just as much
Yes, I faked it.
Nineteen years ago...
I faked drowning...
hoping that you would come to rescue me.
You used to always come to my rescue.
Kashi, if I were to...
fake drowning again...
would you...
I have to take this. Sorry.
- Hello.
- It's a DNA match, Singh.
I found Leo's iPad, bro.
It has more than 100 photos
and videos of club members.
Did you tell anyone else?
Hello, Bambi ji.
I just received the DNA report
for the skeleton.
It matches your husband, Anshul.
Is Lawyer sahab there with you?
I need to ask him something.
Hello, Bambi ji, can you hear me?
Do one thing.
Wait for me. I am coming.
Just stay there, alright?
Bambi ji, answer me!
Is Lawyer sahab with you?
No.
Okay. It isn't polite
to keep repeating the same thing...
Where is your son?
He has left for Kolkata.
Can we get Koohu's number?
- Number...
- We have never spoken to her.
Cookie ji had given you a present.
A bust of Mother Teresa.
Can you tell me where it is?
It has been missing for a long time.
- Padam.
- Yes, sir.
Lawyer sahab has not left for Kolkata.
- Track his phone.
- Yes, sir.
What are you saying?
Raks!
Send someone
to Shepherd's Home Orphanage immediately!
What did he want
with the Mother Teresa bust?
Where is Warden Raks's room?
Do you know what happened to Padam once?
Padam was assigned a case
where a Mercedes
had run over a poor rickshaw driver.
Everyone asked him to drop the case.
"He was a poor man, a small man."
But Padam said, "No!"
The price of cars may vary,
but the value
of the lives inside is equal.
So, in your durbar,
there may be differences
between big and small, rich and poor.
But today, in our assembly,
you are all equal.
So, please sit down.
The ones who are standing,
please sit down.
Now this looks democratic.
Let me go. I was called here!
SP!
I don't remember calling you here.
I know.
I tried to call you...
Shehnaz ji, I caught your lie
the day you spoke of that riot.
...to try and give birth
after enduring 14 hours of pain
in the middle of a burning chawl,
with sword-wielding rioters
at his doorstep!
And then...
The riot that fits your story
was Mumbai 1992.
Back then, you were...
My apologies.
I am about to mention a lady's age.
Sixteen years old.
Which doesn't match
your daughters' current ages.
My mom didn't even let me
see the child's face.
However, I found out the child
was placed in Shepherd's Home Orphanage.
As I progressed in my career,
I made a conscious effort
not to look back.
Yet, I continued donating to Shepherd's.
Then, one day, Leo showed up.
He knew who my son was.
He had his photos.
He started blackmailing me.
His condition was
for me to acknowledge my son
in front of everyone,
or else he would reveal everything
to my daughters.
So, today, I told them myself.
Shehnaz ji wasn't,
but Raja ji was being blackmailed
by Leo ji solely for the money.
I can't do this to Thinsuk.
His life will be ruined.
It has nothing to do with this murder.
It is his personal matter.
It might be his personal matter,
for all I care,
but Guppie Ram was killed with his gun.
With deep regret,
I must tell you it was a suicide.
Forensic evidence
and blood splatter reports confirm it.
Forensics also revealed a shocking detail
about the dead body
buried in the kitchen garden.
I have already informed Bambi ji.
It was her husband Anshul ji's body.
We have matched his DNA with his parents.
Through Anshul ji's skeleton,
we discovered yet another thing.
The cause of death
was a deep wound on his head.
He was attacked. By who?
- Padam.
- Yes, sir.
"I am sorry for everything, Bambi."
"I love you. I always have."
Yesterday, Yash tried to kill himself.
By overdosing on drugs.
Right now, he's in a coma.
Yash ji has been crazy about Bambi ji
ever since they were kids.
We found out that he used to stalk her
and spy on her.
Yash couldn't stand
Bambi ji's new relationship,
so he decided to take out
Anshul ji himself.
However, he couldn't do it alone,
and Guppie Ram ji became his accomplice.
- Druggie bastard!
- Shut up!
Just shut up!
I knew this was coming! I knew it!
That's why I abandoned my dying son
in the hospital and came here!
You all are scoundrels! Bloody scoundrels!
Nobody cares for anyone here!
Everyone is...
Don't... I know what you guys say
about me behind my back.
Gold-digging pile of dung!
Wretched leach!
- Rosh...
- Stop it!
My favorite. Blood-sucker cat.
Today, I'll show you
what sort of a cat I am!
I dare you to come near my Yash!
I will scratch your eyes off!
I won't spare you!
Roshni ji, calm down.
Let's, for a moment,
consider that Yash ji is not the killer.
This is Leo ji's device.
He used to always
keep his camera switched on
so that he could capture
the weaknesses of his prey
and then blackmail them.
Look at the date
and time stamps in this video.
This is Bambi ji
and Anshul ji's anniversary night.
At 2:30 a.m.
In this video,
we came across a very interesting thing.
Which perhaps even Leo ji didn't catch.
Look at this.
Far in the back, there's a car parked,
which has a huge dent on the trunk.
We all can easily recognize
whose car it is.
Lawyer sahab.
Lawyer sahab might have left
the anniversary party early,
but he returned late at night.
Veins surging with passion and alcohol
more than blood.
He was so drunk
that burying the body became difficult.
So, Guppie Ram ji became his accomplice.
Coincidentally,
the bus that Anshul ji and his friends
were supposed to board
to the mountains fell into a deep valley.
No one realized
that Anshul ji never boarded the bus.
Yes, I did go back to the club
that night to meet Bambi.
I knocked on the door,
but no one answered, so I went back home.
The story you're trying to spin
might work here, but not in court.
It will, Lawyer sahab.
I'll make it work.
The CCTV footage of the night
of October 12th has been deleted.
Your murder weapon,
the bust of Mother Teresa,
has been missing from your house
for the past three years.
When you were attacking Ajay Kumar,
you gained information
about many sources that trade Pinko.
Sir, but Yash's letter.
He has confessed.
We may never know if he wrote it
or if Lawyer sahab made him write it.
But Kashi was not even in the club.
How could he have
switched the protein bottles?
He didn't.
Guppie Ram ji did.
That's why the bottle found its way
to the cat named Prince Harry.
My apologies, Lawyer sahab.
Let's go.
Get up.
Oh Lord, my Almighty!
Born to one, now taken away by another
Sir, you pulled off a miracle today.
You apprehended the murderer,
saved the beggar king,
and, in addition, coerced them
into revealing everything.
Sir.
We haven't untangled every single knot
in this case yet, Padam.
- What?
- ACP sir!
Voilà!
I need to share something
with you, ACP sir.
I love the Club.
I know people like you
won't understand this,
but I love every single thing about RDC.
It's the privileged world I was born into.
And it's the only world I have known.
Oh Lord, my Almighty!
Born to one, now taken away by another
So many of us have nowhere else to go.
We're so terrified of the real world,
we've made the Club
our own little universe.
It's my home. My prison.
And what a beautiful fucking prison.
Anshul was perfect husband material.
Sweet, dependable, rich, and so on.
But there was just one problem.
He was not Kashi.
I just needed one thing from him.
To present the image
of a perfect couple. That's it.
You know, for the Club.
He couldn't even do that.
You're leaving me?
You're leaving me for a maid?
For a fucking maid, Anshul!
I left you a long time ago, Bambi.
And like I said, I fucking love her.
I don't care if you love her!
Love her, fuck her,
do whatever the fuck you want!
But do it in your room!
The world... Fuck the world!
The Club cannot find out about this!
Do you understand what I am...
Is that the only thing that
you give a fuck about?
Haven't you learned anything
from your parents' relationship?
You're so fucking selfish, Anshul!
You're so fucking selfish!
Have you thought about Ganga?
Do you think people will accept her?
She won't even get membership
at the Club, Anshul.
You're so stupid!
Do you really think
I give a fuck if she gets membership?
- You should give a fuck!
- I don't!
"I love her."
Marriage is built on love, not on status.
Love has nothing
to do with marriage, Anshul!
What would that fool know about love?
Look at me, sir.
I loved Kashi but didn't marry him.
You need to understand what I'm saying.
No one is going to accept her.
Listen to me.
We have a perfect marriage.
We don't, Bambi.
Are you fucking hearing yourself?
We have a perfect marriage, Anshul.
We don't.
It doesn't matter, Anshul.
It doesn't fucking matter!
What does love have to do with marriage?
Kashi is a dumbfuck.
He never understood this either.
Anshul, please listen to me.
You listen to me.
The divorce papers are almost ready.
Once I come back from my...
Convincing Guppie to help me was easy.
I just told him
that Anshul had raped Ganga.
I had a lot of love for Guppie. I promise.
But what can one do?
These people are never truly our own.
They lack the capacity to comprehend
their own interests and losses.
That bastard Leo had it though.
Once you kill someone,
murder becomes a part
of your list of solutions.
- Bambi, did you hear that song?
- What song?
Where is it coming from?
It wasn't your fault, Guppie.
You are unwell.
That's the reason.
I'm like your daughter, aren't I?
Would you like it if...
I get sent to the gallows because of you?
If there was a way out,
you would have surely helped me.
If only Yash had not
cleaned out the Pinko I had planted,
he would've just ended up in jail,
not in the ICU.
Everything could have been resolved
if you hadn't stuck
your middle-class nose in.
Now it's my turn, Bambi ji.
Because only conversations
can untangle the knots.
- Yes, Granny.
- Return gift.
I got rid of the gift.
At night, that statue used
to stare at me like an owl.
So, who did you give the statue to?
The Todis' daughter.
So, have you ever been on this train?
I didn't want Kashi to know.
Your peculiar interest in this case
and the mild rumble
in my stomach kept telling me
that you're the murderer.
If you need anything, give me a call.
I will sign for it.
But I had no evidence against you.
Then I remembered
that I had an ace up my sleeve.
Lawyer sahab.
No matter how far a person falls,
when it comes to love,
the inherent goodness
within them naturally surfaces.
I told you,
the world's most complicated riddle is
love.
The more I try to forget you
I remember you just as much
My life slips away
I know, Professor sahab.
And that riddle never gets solved.
That's why I know
that I will find a good lawyer
who will come to visit me every day.
For years to come.
- One more thing.
- Yes.
Get that massive cement planter.
It's carrot season.
If we grow carrots,
we'll get great results.
How about trying gourds?
Lawyer sahab,
don't take on Bambi ji's case.
That night,
why did you go to the orphanage?
To check if Bambi had left any evidence?
What would you have done if you found any?
Lawyer sahab, you have a big heart.
Trim it down a bit.
Return to that Bengali girl in Kolkata.
Lawyer sahab!
I hope Koohu ji is real!
This case was way more complex
than any we've tackled before, Padam.
Not only were we solving a murder case,
but also unraveling
the knots of a love story.
A strange love story.
Sir, may I park it?
No, I will do it.
You go and check on our snacks.
Add a little more spice...
Do you know what happened to Padam once?